(Sheldon:)For an evening of passing a bottle
of fortified wine around a trash can...
(Sheldon:)...you look great.
(Sheldon:)What am I thinking? Whiskers.
(Penny:)Oh, hey, if we hurry we can make
the Jennifer Aniston movie.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, uh,
there's also an amazing documentary...
...about building a dam on a river
in South America.
(Penny:)Okay, but the Jennifer Aniston movie
has Jennifer Aniston.
(Penny:)And she's not building a dam.
- Can't argue with that. I'll get the tickets.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)Actually, you know what?
(Leonard:)I think it's about time
I pick a movie we see.
Wha?... You picked plenty of movies.
(Leonard:)No, you always picked
and it was always the same.